[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しん ごう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Світлофор"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'みぎ (へ|に), ひだり (へ|に)' read in word?",
        "answer": "Поверніть, будь ласка, на…"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'うんてんしゅ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Водій"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'つかれました' read in word?",
        "answer": "Втомитися"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'びょういん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Лікарня"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しめます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Закривати, закрито"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'やっきょく' read in word?",
        "answer": "Аптека"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'といいました' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сказав “～”"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'まっすぐ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Прямо"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おつり' read in word?",
        "answer": "Решта"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とても' read in word?",
        "answer": "Дуже"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぐうぜん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Випадково"
    }
]
